[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the very first cat show held?", "correct_answer": "1895", "incorrect_answers": ["1926", "1877", "1901"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these comedy teams consists of a husband and wife, whose son is an Emmy Award-winning actor?", "correct_answer": "Stiller and Meara", "incorrect_answers": ["Bergen and McCarthy", "Burns and Allen", "Shields and Yarnell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does sciaphobia mean fear of blood?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Islamic beliefs, the Devil was created out of what?", "correct_answer": "Smokeless fire", "incorrect_answers": ["Unbreakable rocks", "Clay", "Polluted soil"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word graffiti comes from this language.", "correct_answer": "Italian", "incorrect_answers": ["Spanish", "Portuguese", "French"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important work connected to color theory did the international group of experts known as the Commission Internationale de leclairage (CIE) create in 1931?", "correct_answer": "Developed a mathematical model of color", "incorrect_answers": ["Mapped the frequency of basic colors in the spectrum", "Developed the color model of the universe", "Defined the primary, secondary, and tertiary colors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the psychopathic killer in the 2000 movie American Psycho based on the book by Bret Easton Ellis?", "correct_answer": "Patrick Bateman", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Dorf", "Jason Bateman", "John Higgins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The chances of having twins in the 21st century are ...?", "correct_answer": "3 in 100", "incorrect_answers": ["15 in 100", "10 in 100", "5 in 100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the hilarious movie Wedding Crashers first hit the movie theatres in the United States?", "correct_answer": "2005", "incorrect_answers": ["2006", "2004", "1999"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas OMalley from the movie The Aristocats has more than one name. Which of these is one of his names?", "correct_answer": "DeLacey", "incorrect_answers": ["DeCasey", "DeLaSoul", "DeVilliers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This horror film focuses on a successful criminal psychologist who awakens to find herself a patient in the mental institution she has worked for.", "correct_answer": "Gothica", "incorrect_answers": ["American Gothic", "The Eye", "Exorcist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Flashlight fish, has a light-producing organ, which contains luminescent bacteria. Where is this organ located?", "correct_answer": "Below the eye of the fish", "incorrect_answers": ["On the dorsal fin of the fish", "Above the eye of the fish", "Between the eyes of the fish"]}]